

PROFILE

As a highly motivated and skilled Mobile Developer with near 3 years of expertise in utilizing Flutter. I am eager to take on Junior - Middle Mobile role where I can further enhance my knowledge, develop my technical skills, and work collaboratively with a team of professionals. My passion for learning new languages and technologies, combined with my strong work ethic, make me an ideal candidate for this position.

CONTACT

PHONE: 0348098023

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/ngduonganhhuy/

FMAII:

ngduonganhhuy@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO:

Holmes Website

LANGUAGES

English – Reading, Listening, Speaking

EDUCATION

From 08/2018 - 05/2022

Saigon Technology University

Recent GPA: 3.4 - 3.44

NGUYEN DUONG ANH HUY

WORK EXPERIENCE

Playground (Playgroundx.site)

Web Developer

March 2021 - September 2021

- Manage tasks via Trello
- Building landing page according to designer's mockup

Exnodes (Exnodes.vn)

Mobile Developer

September 2021 – September 2022

- Develop app according to designer's mockup on Figma, complete user-story according to BA's arrangement and manage time to complete task on JIRA.
- Source Code Management and learning more about DevOps with AWS amazon (CodeCommit), handle image with s3 Bucket
- Coding UI/UX, integration API with Flutter, GETX, JWT, Bloc,,...
- Configuration for building app on Android and IOS

GMO Runsystem (Runsystem.net)

Mobile Developer

September 2022 - Present

- Define user-story according to BA's arrangement
- Provide solutions to support other members
- Design according to defined user-story, develop app according this design on Adobe XD, Figma
- Configuration for building app on Android and IOS for testing over third application (Testflight, Diawi)
- Deploy app to CHPlay and AppStore

BHD (BHDStar.vn)

Mobile Developer

April 2024 - Present

- Improve UX, Optimize product (Danet)
- Support content team
- Design according to defined user-story, develop app according this design on Figma
- Build new product (DShorts)
- Deploy app to CHPlay, AppStores

TECHNICAL SKILLS

PROGRAMING LANGUAGES

- HTML, CSS
- JS
- Dart
- Swift

FRAMEWORKS/PLATFORMS

- React Native (Typescript, Redux)
- Flutter (GetX, Bloc, Riverpod)
- Swift UI, UI Kit
- NodeJS

DATABASE MANAGEMENT SYSTEMS

- MongoDB
- MySQL

VERSION CONTROL

- GIT, Code Commit, Gitlab

PROJECT SHOWCASE

BIZBOOKLY CUSTOMER (2021 – SEP 2022) – Mobile Developer

Description:

 A cutting-edge and user-friendly scheduling application for seamlessly booking appointment at salon, streamlining operations and improving customer experience

Technologies:

- Back-end: Python, MySQL
- Mobile: Flutter (GetX)

Responsibilities:

- Build a customer app from scratch using flutter
- Configuration HTTP to handle Restful API Integrate JWT to authorization and authentication
- Setup the environment for build app different platforms
- Setup FCM

AppStore: <u>Bizbookly</u> CH-Play: <u>Bizbookly</u>

BIZBOOKLY STAFF (2021 – SEP 2022) – Mobile Developer

Description:

 An advanced scheduling management app for efficiently organizing and coordinating the schedules of staff members

Technologies:

- Back-end: Python, MySQL
- Mobile: Flutter (GetX)

Responsibilities:

- Build a customer app from scratch using flutter
- Configuration HTTP to handle Restful API Integrate JWT to authorization and authentication
- Setup the environment for build app different platforms
- Setup FCM

AppStore: <u>Bizbookly Staff</u> CH-Play: Bizbookly Staff

Yakult Khai Thác (SEP 2022 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

A staff's app for converting from paper processes to app processes for easier task management
 Technologies:

- Front-end: AngularJS
- Back-end: Laravel, MySQL
- Mobile: Flutter (Bloc)

Responsibilities:

Define and design user-flow according file excel from customer on Adobe XD

- Build app from design
- Configuration DIO to handle Restful API Integrate JWT to authorization and authentication
- Setup the environment for build app different platforms
- Setup FCM
- Deploy app on Testflight, build APK for QC testing

Gonsa Trung Tâm Dược Phẩm (SEP 2022 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

An e-commerce project for buying and selling pharmaceutical products through B2B & B2C

Technologies:

- Front-end: AngularJS
- Back-end: Wordpress, MySQL
- Mobile: Flutter (Bloc)

Responsibilities:

- Build app from design
- Configuration DIO to handle Restful API Integrate JWT to authorization and authentication
- Setup the environment for build app different platforms
- Setup FCM
- Payment with NeoPay
- Deploy app on Testflight, build APK for QC testing
- Deploy app to CHPlay and AppStore

AppStore: <u>Trung tâm dược phẩm</u> CH-Play: <u>Trung tâm dược phẩm</u>

Smart Staff (NOV 2023 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

This is a time work app for MacOS

Technologies:

Mobile: Swift

Responsibilities:

Do tasks

Direct Sales (OCT 2023 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

This is a direct sales app designed to replace traditional paper-based processes

Technologies:

- Front-end: AngularJS
- Back-end: NodeJS, MongoDB
- Mobile: React native

Responsibilities:

- Design app
- Building boilerplate
- Configuration RTK query
- Setup the environment for build app different platforms
- Setup FCM
- Offline feature

GLOPR Chat App (JUNE 2023 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

A chat app from glopr team

Technologies:

- Front-end: ReactJS
- Back-end: NestJS, MongoDB
- Mobile:
 - o Multi-Platform: Flutter
 - o Single-Platform: Kotlin, Swift

Responsibilities:

- Build app from design
- Deploy app to CHPlay and AppStore

Danet (April 2024 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

Movies watching app

Technologies:

Front-end: ReactJS

Back-end: NodeJS, MongoDB

Mobile: Flutter

Responsibilities:

- Fix bugs
- Improve UX, optimize
- Build new features
- Deploy to market

AppStore: <u>DANET</u> CH-Play: <u>DANET</u>

DShorts (April 2024 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

Short-Movies watching app

Technologies:

Front-end: ReactJS

Back-end: NodeJS, MongoDB

Mobile: Flutter

Responsibilities:

Setup google services (Firebase, Admob, Ads, ...)

Build new features

Deploy to market

AppStore: DShorts
CH-Play: DShorts

LendMe (April 2024 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

Pawn shop management app

Technologies:

Front-end: Flutter

Mobile: Flutter

Responsibilities:

Build UI following design on Figma

Integration PayOS to app

Deploy to market

Website: LendMe

Kibiaccessories (Graduation Project)

Description:

Ecommerce – accessories store

Technologies:

- Front-end: React & Redux, ES6, AntD Client, MUI Admin
- Back-end: NodeJS (Express), MongoDB

Responsibilities:

- Build a Back-end server using ExpressJS & Mongoose
- Build a web app for customer using React, Redux & AntD
- Upload images with firebase storage

- Config Axios to handle Restful API
- Integrate login with Google, Facebook payment with Momo, Stripe API

ARTICLES

BEST PRACTICES WRITING CLEAN CODE WITH FLUTTER (this article)